RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Permitting, Enforcement, and Remediation Division, 1928-1979; bulk 1969-1977
    - Correspondence Files, 1997-050
      - New Britain (Box 66)
        - Stop & Go Transmission (Box 67)
        - Tuttle & Baily/Div of Allied Thermal Corp., 2 folders (Box 67)
        - U-Haul (Box 67)
        - Winslow Automotics, Inc. (Box 67)
        - Union Mfg. Co. (Box 67)
      - New Canaan (Box 67)
        - New Canaan Misc, 4 folders (Box 67)
        - American-European Auto Repair (Box 68)
        - Conron Residence (Box 68)
        - New Canaan Housing Authority (Box 68)
        - Karl Chevrolet Co. (Box 68)
        - Miller’s Farm Dairy (Box 68)
        - New Canaan Neighborhood Inc., 2 folders (Box 68)
        - New Canaan Water Co., 3 folders (Box 68)
        - Arne Thune (Box 68)
        - Yankee Housewright Inc. (Box 68)
      - New Fairfield (Box 68)
        - New Fairfield Misc, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - New Fairfield Auto Body Shop (Box 68)
        - New Fairfield High School (Box 68)
        - Squantz Pond State Park, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Waters Edge (Box 68)
        - A.J. Weil Excavating, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Viking Aluminum Products (Box 68)
      - New Hartford (Box 68)
        - New Hartford Misc., 3 folders (Box 68)
        - New Hartford Siltation & Erosion (Box 68)
        - New Hartford Subsurface Problems, 2 folders (Box 68)
        - Birch Ridge (Box 68)
        - Canton Valley Realty (Box 68)
        - Country Motors Inc. (Box 68)
        - Hitchcock Chair Co. (Box 68)
        - Mountain Laurel Develop (Box 68)
        - Pine Brook Dev. (Box 69)
        - Poroco Imported Car Parts (Box 69)
        - New Hartford Siltation & Erosion (Box 69)
        - Sollitto Subdivision (Box 69)
        - Steele Rd. Subdivision (Box 69)
        - Union Pin - Hearing (Box 69)
        - West Hill Rd. (Box 69)
        - Waring Products, 4 folders (Box 69)
      - New Haven (Box 69)
        - New Haven Misc, 4 folders (Box 69)
        - New Haven Town of, 4 folders (Box 69)
        - New Haven Subsurface Problem (Box 69)
        - Ct Hard Rubber Co. (Box 69)
        - New Haven STP, 2 folders (Box 70)
        - New Haven Town of (Box 70)
        - New Haven Sewers (Box 70)
        - New Haven prior to, 1939 (Box 70)
        - New Haven prior to, 1946 (Box 70)
        - Ace Plating Co., 2 folders (Box 70)
        - Adley Maintenance Bldg (Box 70)
        - Alco Auto Center Inc. (Box 70)
        - American Microfilm Service (Box 70)
        - American Steel & Wire (Box 70)
        - AMTRAK (Box 70)
        - Armstrong Rubber (Box 70)
        - Atlantic Richfield Co., 4 folders (Box 70)
        - Barney Oil Co/Div of Goodrich Oil (Box 70)
        - Barnick & Son Deisel Works (Box 70)
        - Blonders, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Brothers Harley-Davidson, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Blue Jay Cleaners & Laundry, Inc. (Box 70)
        - C. Cowles & Co. (Box 70)
        - Centennial Auto Sales (Box 70)
        - Chet’s Auto Parts (Box 70)
        - Columbus Auto Body Works (Box 70)
        - Cycle Salvage, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Cerro Wire & Cable Co/Rockbestos Co. (Box 71)
        - Chevron Oil Co. (Box 71)
        - Claud Ann Marina (Box 71)
        - Conrail (Box 71)
        - Cott Beverage Co. (Box 71)
        - C. Cowles & Co., 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Dosch - King (Box 71)
        - Eaton Corp. (Box 71)
        - ESPT/New Haven Water Co. (Box 71)
        - Exxon Co. (Box 71)
        - Exxon Corp. (Box 71)
        - Exxon Car Wash (Box 71)
        - Exxon/JBT Switches (Box 71)
        - Fantasy Auto Painting & Body Works (Box 71)
        - Federal Paper Board Co., 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Federal Paper Board Co - Hearing (Box 71)
        - Getty Oil, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Geometric Tool/United-Greenfield Div. Of TRW, Inc. (Box 71)
        - Gilbert’s Auto Body Clinic (Box 71)
        - Giordano Construction (Box 71)
        - Gulf Oil Co., 2 folders (Box 71)
        - H. B. Ives, Inc., 3 folders (Box 71)
        - H. Krevit & Co. (Box 71)
        - Humble Oil & Refining, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - A. B. Hendryx Co. (Box 71)
        - Hoffman Fuel Co. (Box 71)
        - Ives Division Leight Products, Inc. (Box 71)
        - Indus Waste Treatment/Mite Corp. (Box 71)
        - J. & J. Cars, Inc. (Box 71)
        - JBT Switches (Box 71)
        - J. C. Auto Sales (Box 71)
        - Kroll Coal & Oil Co. (Box 71)
        - Lighthouse Point Bath Houses (Box 71)
        - A. C. Gilbert (Box 71)
        - M. B. Electronics A Textron Co. (Box 71)
        - M. B. Electronics/A Textron Co. (Box 72)
        - New Haven Mill River, 2 folders (Box 72)
        - Mite Corp., 2 folders (Box 72)
        - Mobil Oil Co. (Box 72)
        - M & R Goffe St Service Station (Box 72)
        - New Haven Municipal Collection System (Box 72)
        - Mobil Oil Corp. (Box 72)
        - National Gypsum Co. (Box 72)
        - National Passenger Rail Corp. (Box 72)
        - New Haven Harbor (Box 72)
        - New Haven Terminal (Box 72)
        - New Haven Water Co. (Box 72)
        - New Haven Malleable Iron Co. (Box 72)
        - Parkridge Tower Apt. (Box 72)
        - Penn Central (Box 72)
        - Petrillo’s Used Auto Parts (Box 72)
        - Olin Corp., 5 folders (Box 72)
        - New Haven Redevelopment Agency (Box 72)
        - Reliance Mfg. (Box 72)
        - Saleway Texaco Steam & Clean (Box 72)
        - Sargent & Co., 4 folders (Box 72)
        - Seamless Rubber Co., 3 folders (Box 72)
        - Simkins Industries, 2 folders (Box 72)
        - Stop & Go Transmission (Box 72)
        - Southern CT Gas Co., 4 folders (Box 72)
        - Sperry & Barnes (Box 72)
        - Texaco, Inc. (Box 72)
        - Union Pump Station (Box 72)
        - Terrace Auto Sales (Box 72)
        - TRW Geometric Tool Division (Box 72)
        - U-Haul (Box 72)
        - Universal Auto Sales (Box 72)
        - Verrillo & Petrozzoli Repair (Box 72)
        - VIP Service Center (Box 72)
        - C.W. Blakeslee (Box 72)
        - United Illuminating/Coke Works Plant, 3 folders (Box 73)
        - United Illuminating/English Station Reports, 3 folders (Box 73)
        - United Illuminating/English Station, 6 folders (Box 73)
        - UI/Coke Works Plants, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - U.S. Steel, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Wyatt, Inc. (Box 74)
      - Newington (Box 74)
        - Newington Firehouses (Box 74)
        - Newington Misc, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Newington Subsurface Problems (Box 74)
        - Accurate Brazing Co. (Box 74)
        - American Totalization (Box 74)
        - Atlantic Machine Tool Works, 4 folders (Box 74)
        - Atrax Div/Wallace Murray Corp. (Box 74)
        - Balf Co., 3 folders (Box 74)
        - Batchelder Chair Co., Inc. (Box 74)
        - Battisons Dry Cleaners (Box 74)
        - Coral Tool & Machine Co., 4 folders (Box 74)
        - Complete Rider Inc. (Box 74)
        - Custom Metal Crafters, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Atrax Div. Of Wallace Murray Corp. (Box 74)
        - C & C Automotive Service, Inc. (Box 74)
        - Crest Pontiac Cadilliac (Box 74)
        - Custom Metal Crafters, Inc., 3 folders (Box 74)
        - Atlantic Machine Tool (Box 74)
        - Dowing and Perkins (Box 74)
        - Exxon Car Wash (Box 74)
        - Fafnir Bearing Co., 3 folders (Box 74)
        - Fenn Mfg. (Box 74)
        - H. O Penn, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Glenwood Auto Body (Box 74)
        - International Motorcycle Repair (Box 74)
        - Ivy Hill Shopping Center (Box 74)
        - Keeney Mfg. Co., 3 folders (Box 74)
        - Loctite Corp. (Box 74)
        - MAC Equipment (Box 74)
        - Mediplex of Newington (Box 74)
        - Mediplex of Newington/Hearing (Box 74)
        - Miller & Co., Inc. (Box 74)
        - Mobil Oil Corp. (Box 74)
        - Mobile Truck Services (Box 74)
        - Newington Childrens Hospital (Box 74)
        - Yankee Milk, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Podunk, Inc. (Box 74)
        - Sun Oil Co. (Box 74)
        - United Illuminating, 2 folders (Box 74)
        - Varneys Auto Radiatory & Body (Box 74)
        - Veeder Industries (Box 74)
      - New London (Box 75)
        - New London Misc (Box 75)
        - New London Harbor Oil Pollution Committee (Box 75)
        - State Pier (Box 75)
        - Municipal Landfill (Box 75)
        - Auto Body of New London (Box 75)
        - New London Auto Works (Box 75)
        - B & S Cycle (Box 75)
        - Barry’s Cleaners (Box 75)
        - Blonders Auto Parts (Box 75)
        - Commercial Engraving Co. (Box 75)
        - Crown Mfg. (Box 75)
        - Electric Boat Facility (Box 75)
        - Navel Underwater Systems Center/New London Lab (Box 75)
        - Navel Sub Base (Box 75)
        - New London Pump Station (Box 75)
        - Speedy Muffler King (Box 75)
        - Steil Mill (Box 75)
        - Thames River Pollution Abatement Committee (Box 75)
        - Universal Gypsum Co., Inc. - Hearing (Box 75)
        - Thames River Dredging Project (Box 75)
        - USCGA Waterfront (Box 75)
        - USS Fulton (Box 75)
      - New Milford (Box 75)
        - New Milford Misc, 2 folders (Box 75)
        - New Milford Town of /Land Application, 2 folders (Box 75)
        - Beth Mor Sand & Gravel, 3 folders (Box 76)
        - Burndy Corp., 2 folders (Box 76)
        - J Beers Assoc - Hearing (Box 76)
        - Bills Garage (Box 76)
        - BRT Corp. (Box 76)
        - Candlewood Country Club Courts (Box 76)
        - Coach Auto Body (Box 76)
        - Century Brass Products, 2 folders (Box 76)
        - Carlo’s Auto Repair (Box 76)
        - Conn’s Dairy (Box 76)
        - Diventco, Inc. (Box 76)
        - Diventco, Inc., 2 folders (Box 77)
        - Eronel Services (Box 77)
        - Flynn Fann (Box 77)
        - George the Giant Car Wash (Box 77)
        - W T Grants - Hearing (Box 77)
        - Harry & Sons (Box 77)
        - Hull Funeral Service (Box 77)
        - Alfred Grammatico (Box 77)
        - Kimberly Clark Corp., 6 folders (Box 77)
        - John=s Foreign Car Repair (Box 77)
        - E Paul Kovacs (Box 77)
        - Nestles Co., 3 folders (Box 77)
        - New Milford Water Co., 2 folders (Box 77)
        - Newton Wire Corp. (Box 78)
        - Northville General Store (Box 78)
        - New Milford Oil Spill (Box 78)
        - Photronics, Inc. (Box 78)
        - Pleasant View Subdiv. (Box 78)
        - New Milford Refuse Disposal (Box 78)
        - Robertson Bleachery & Dye Works (Box 78)
        - New Milford SCA Landfill (Box 78)
        - Scovill (Box 78)
        - Sega Sand & Gravel, 3 folders (Box 78)
        - SKA Assoc., Inc. - Hearing (Box 78)
        - J. P. Stevens & Co., 5 folders (Box 78)
        - South End Service Station (Box 78)
        - New Milford Subsurface Problems (Box 78)
        - New Milford Siltation & Erosion (Box 78)
        - Sunny Valley Farm, 10 folders (Box 78)
        - Teknicircuits (Box 78)
        - Thomas Scott Car Wash (Box 78)
        - Trailer Park/Candlewood Mt. Rd. (Box 78)
        - Tri-Par Finishing Corp. (Box 78)
        - Winchester Electronics, 3 folders (Box 78)
      - Newtown (Box 79)
        - Newtown Misc., 2 folders (Box 79)
        - Newtown Town of (Sanitary Service), 2 folders (Box 79)
        - Newtown Siltation & Erosion, 2 folders (Box 79)
        - Newtown Board of Ed (Box 79)
        - Newtown Oil Spill Reports (Box 79)
        - Newtown Subsurface Problem (Box 79)
        - Allied Container Corp. (Box 79)
        - Batchelder Chars Co. (Box 79)
        - Cappy Brothers Sand & Gravel (Box 79)
        - Consumers Petroleum, 2 folders (Box 79)
        - D’Addario Sand & Gravel (Box 79)
        - Dairy Specialties (Box 79)
        - Eagle Hill Alcoholism Treatment Center (Box 79)
        - Fabric Fire Hose Co., 2 folders (Box 79)
        - Fairfield Hills Hospital, 3 folders (Box 79)
        - F W Trench Tube Co. (Box 79)
        - Harvey Hubbell, Inc., 3 folders (Box 79)
        - Lufkin Farm (Poverty Hollow Rd.) (Box 79)
        - Marlo Co., Inc. (Box 79)
        - Cyril Montell (Box 79)
        - Meadow Brook Terrace Trailer Park (Box 79)
        - Newman (Box 79)
        - Newtown High School STP, 2 folders (Box 79)
        - Newtown High School (Box 79)
        - Pootatuck Pollution (Box 79)
        - Thor Plastics Corp. (Box 79)
        - Uniroyal (Box 80)
        - Wee Wash It (Box 80)
        - Newtown, Southbury, Woodbury Study, 1976 (Box 80)
      - Norfolk (Box 80)
        - Norfolk Misc, 3 folders (Box 80)
        - General Electric Co. (Box 80)
        - Society of Brothers, 3 folders (Box 80)
        - James Torrant, 2 folders (Box 80)
      - North Branford (Box 80)
        - North Branford Misc, 3 folders (Box 80)
        - North Branford Post Hearing Comments (Box 80)
        - North Branford Landfill (Box 80)
        - Automated Compaction System (Box 80)
        - B & J Auto Service Center (Box 80)
        - Cinque Brothers (Box 80)
        - Forte’s Meat Market (Box 80)
        - Harry’s Northford Garage (Box 80)
        - Harry Cascio Sales (Box 80)
        - Mrs. Wallace Litwin Complaint (Box 80)
        - Mauro’s Construction Co (Box 80)
        - Mauro’s Construction Co. - Hearing (Box 80)
        - New Haven Trap Rock Co., 2 folders (Box 80)
        - North Branford Auto Body (Box 80)
        - Picker Corp., 4 folders (Box 80)
        - R & J Garage (Box 80)
      - North Canaan (Box 81)
        - North Canaan Misc. (Box 81)
        - North Canaan Siltation and Erosion (Box 81)
        - Becton Dickinson & Co, 2 folders (Box 81)
        - Canaan & Tire and Auto (Box 81)
        - David Jacques (Box 81)
        - Pfizer Inc., 4 folders (Box 81)
      - North Haven (Box 81)
        - North Haven Town Dump (Box 81)
        - North Haven, Town of, 2 folders (Box 81)
        - North Haven Misc, 2 folders (Box 81)
        - Advanced Products Co, 4 folders (Box 81)
        - American Powered Metals (Box 81)
        - American Powered Metals Engineering Report (Box 81)
        - Atlantic Richfield Co. - Hearing, 1975 June (Box 81)
        - Axton Cross Co., 3 folders (Box 81)
        - Briawood Hill Apts (Box 81)
        - Branford Wire & Mfg. Co. Inc. (Box 81)
        - Universal Wire (Box 81)
        - Broadway Auto Sales (Box 81)
        - Burndy Corp, 3 folders (Box 81)
        - Chuck & Eddie Scrap Dealers (Box 81)
        - Cableware Systems - Hearing (Box 81)
        - Circuit Wise, 5 folders (Box 81)
        - No Haven Coach & Carriage (Box 81)
        - Cableware Systems, Inc. (Box 81)
        - Circuit Wise, Inc. (Box 81)
        - Citgo Station (Box 81)
        - City Printing Co. (Box 81)
        - Data Documents, Inc. (Box 81)
        - Diversified Develop Corp - Hearing, 1973 January; 3 folders (Box 81)
        - G & H Equipment (Box 81)
        - Gilberts & Richards, Inc. (Box 81)
        - Humphrey Chemical Co., 3 folders (Box 81)
        - Imprint Realty (Box 81)
        - Industrial Trucks Inc. (Box 81)
        - Interfaith Elderly Housing (Box 81)
        - Jeff’s Power (Box 81)
        - Circuit Wise, 3 folders (Box 82)
        - Knudsen Dairy (Box 82)
        - Marlin Arms, 3 folders (Box 82)
        - O.F. Mossberg & Sons, Inc., 2 folders (Box 82)
        - The Newton Co., 3 folders (Box 82)
        - No. Haven Gas Station Wilber Cross Hwy (Box 82)
        - No. Haven Laundromat (Box 82)
        - P.C. Motors Plasticrete Co., 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Platt-Labonia Co., 4 folders (Box 82)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, 3 folders (Box 82)
        - Spectrogram Corp. - Hearing (Box 82)
        - M. Schiavone & Sons, Inc., 3 folders (Box 82)
        - Union Carbide, 3 folders (Box 82)
        - Stop Shop Supermarket, 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Technical Measurements Corp (Box 82)
        - Tenedine Cider Company (Box 82)
        - United Aluminum Corp. (Box 82)
        - UpJohn Co. Inc. (Box 82)
        - United Smelting & Aluminum Co. (Box 82)
      - North Stonington (Box 83)
        - North Stonington Misc., 2 folders (Box 83)
        - Bob Smith AMC Jeep, Inc. (Box 83)
        - Assekon Swamp & Brook, 2 folders (Box 83)
        - Mystic Green Apts (Groton) (Box 83)
        - Hendels Inc. /Kingswood, Meadowood Central Fuel Destribution System, 2 folders (Box 83)
        - Mobil Service Station (Box 83)
        - Ottawa Silica company, 2 folders (Box 83)
        - Posi-Seal International (Box 83)
        - Christopher Storey (Box 83)
        - Rte I/95 Highway Rest Area (Box 83)
        - Yeerington Auto Salvage (Box 83)
      - Norwalk (Box 83)
        - Town of Norwalk (Box 83)
        - Norwalk Municipal Landfill (Box 83)
        - Norwalk Pollution of Groundwater Smith Well Field (Box 83)
        - Norwalk City of Norwalk (Box 83)
        - Norwalk Five Mile River Study (Box 83)
        - Norwalk Sixth Taxing District (Box 83)
        - Norwalk Appeal - Hearing, 1967 August (Box 83)
        - NorwalkHearing, 2 folders (Box 83)
        - Allied Mufflers, Inc. (Box 83)
        - Atlantic Dying & Finishing (Box 83)
        - Auto Technics (Box 83)
        - Automatic Signal (Box 83)
        - Bloor Auto Speedy Muffler King (Box 83)
        - Bradlees Shopping Center (Box 83)
        - Bridgeport Brass Co., 4 folders (Box 83)
        - Burndy Corp., 4 folders (Box 83)
        - Caldor (Box 84)
        - CT Classic Car Inc. (Box 84)
        - CL&P, 4 folders (Box 84)
        - Cox and Sons (Box 84)
        - Custom Road Pumping Station Daddario (Box 84)
        - Devine Brothers Inc., 4 folders (Box 84)
        - Dip & Strip (Box 84)
        - Duke Lab (Box 84)
        - CL&P (Box 84)
        - Edwards Co. Inc., 2 folders (Box 84)
        - Electric Indicator Co., Inc. (Box 84)
        - Fairfield Container (Box 84)
        - Fallons Twin City Garage (Box 84)
        - Ferro Corp., 2 folders (Box 84)
        - 1st Tax District Water Dept., 2 folders (Box 84)
        - Haas Food Mfg. Corp., 2 folders (Box 84)
        - Holiday Inn (Box 84)
        - Home Oil Co. Oil Spill (Box 84)
        - Home Furniture Corp. (Box 84)
        - Kings Industries Inc., 6 folders (Box 84)
        - J. D. Auto Clinic (Box 85)
        - Kings Ind. Inc. (Box 85)
        - Lee Corp, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - H. P. Littlefield/Five Mile River (Box 85)
        - Lock Cities Plating (Box 85)
        - MBI Inc. (Box 85)
        - Mike’s Auto Body Inc. (Box 85)
        - Midas Muffler (Box 85)
        - Meineke Discount Muffler (Box 85)
        - Misc., 3 folders (Box 85)
        - Norden Div. Of United Aircraft Corp. (Box 85)
        - NEUS Co. (Box 85)
        - Norwalk Dyeing & Finishing (Box 85)
        - Norwalk Foreign Car Services (Box 85)
        - Norwalk Powered Metals Inc. (Box 85)
        - Norwalk Recycling Service Inc. (Box 85)
        - Norwalk State Tech College (Box 85)
        - Pepperidge Farms (Box 85)
        - Perkin-Elmer Corp., 3 folders (Box 85)
        - Plating Specialists, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - Printed Circuits (Box 85)
        - Rowayton Market STP (Box 85)
        - Rowayton Market Pharmacy, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - Sorensen-Raytheon Co. (Box 85)
        - State Oil Co. (Box 85)
        - The Strip Joint (Box 85)
        - Sun Oil Co. (Box 85)
        - Tallmadge Bros. Inc. (Box 85)
        - T-Bar Inc. (Box 85)
        - Town Fair Tire (Box 85)
        - Trans Lux Corp., 3 folders (Box 85)
        - U. S. Surgical Corp. (Box 85)
        - Valentine’s Auto Body Repair Shop (Box 85)
        - Vanderbuilt Gem Co., 2 folders (Box 85)
        - Victor’s Sunoco (Box 85)
        - Yankee Metal Products (Box 85)
      - Norwich (Box 86)
        - Norwich Misc, 2 folders (Box 86)
        - Norwich Landfill (Box 86)
        - Norwich Municipal Sewerage (Box 86)
        - Norwich Public Utility Gas & Electric Plant (Box 86)
        - Supreme Court Decision (Box 86)
        - Norwich 2nd Street (Box 86)
        - Norwich Public Hearing, 1976 July (Box 86)
        - AEG Power Tool Corp, 2 folders (Box 86)
        - Arrow Point (Box 86)
        - Artistic Wire Prod. Co., 2 folders (Box 86)
        - Atlantic Carton Corp. (Box 86)
        - Auralux Corp. (Box 86)
        - Baco Corp. D/b/a Midas Muffler (Box 86)
        - Beit Bros. Pike Plaza (Box 86)
        - Capehart Corp, 4 folders (Box 86)
        - Celluci Car Wash (Box 86)
        - Chambers Storck Co., 2 folders (Box 86)
        - Charc O Broail & Dairy Kreme (Box 86)
        - City Textile Printing Corp. (Box 86)
        - O’Neil, Charles Comm (Box 86)
        - Daisy Print Work (Box 86)
        - Dupont Red Tag Inc., 2 folders (Box 86)
        - Durable Shopping Center (Box 86)
        - Barkers Shopping Center & Pike Plaza (Box 86)
        - Falls Mill Recycling (Box 86)
        - Goldmine Mobil Park (Box 86)
        - Hale Mfg (Box 86)
        - Harvard Acres Subdivision (Box 86)
        - IMR Realty (Box 86)
        - 100 Patient Nursing Home (Box 86)
        - King Seeley Thermos Co., 3 folders (Box 86)
        - Phelps Dodge Copper Products Co. (Box 86)
        - King Seeley Thermos, 5 folders (Box 87)
        - Mallack, 3 folders (Box 87)
        - John Meyer (Box 87)
        - Norms Auto (Box 87)
        - Norwich Hospital (Box 87)
        - Lisbon Textile Prints (Box 87)
        - Masti Kure Products Co./Silver Ins. (Box 87)
        - Norwich Police (Box 87)
        - Norwich Shopping Mall (Box 87)
        - 10 th Street (Box 87)
        - Norwich Occum-Hydro (Box 87)
        - Printed Circuits International (Box 87)
        - Riverview Apt, 2 folders (Box 87)
        - Rogers Pond Landfill (Box 87)
        - Landfill/Yantic River Hollyhock (Box 87)
        - Sinclair-Valentine-Wheelabrator (Box 87)
        - Star St. Aps (Box 87)
        - Stevcokil Co. (Box 87)
        - St. Water Comm vs Norwich (Box 87)
        - Sunnyside Subdivision Pump Sta (Box 87)
        - Norwich Taftville (Box 87)
        - Textile Printing Corp. (Box 87)
        - Thames River Pollution Abatement, 2 folders (Box 87)
        - Trading Cove Motors (Box 87)
        - Uncasville on the Thames Hospital (Box 87)
        - United Metals of CT (Box 87)
        - Urban Renewal Mohegan Village & Mackowicki (Box 87)
        - Yankee Metals Products (Box 87)
      - Old Lyme (Box 87)
        - Old Lyme Misc., 2 folders (Box 87)
        - Ferry Tavern (Box 87)
        - Old Lyme Town Dump (Box 87)
        - Old Lyme - Hearing, 2 folders (Box 87)
        - International Coach Works (Box 87)
        - Old Lyme Old Files - Point of Woods (Box 87)
        - Seafarms Corp. (Box 87)
        - Sheffield Farms (Box 87)
      - Old Saybrook (Box 88)
        - Old Saybrook Misc. (Box 88)
        - Old Saybrook Town of - Hearing, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - Old Saybrook Town Dump (Box 88)
        - Black Swan Marine Corp - Hearing (Box 88)
        - Conrac Corp. - Cramer Div., 2 folders (Box 88)
        - R. R. Donnelley & Sons, 3 folders (Box 88)
        - Eastern Graphics (Box 88)
        - Essex Island Dock & Dredge Co. Inc. (Box 88)
        - Ford Garage (Box 88)
        - New Haven Heat Treating Co. (Box 88)
        - Carl Piontkowski (Box 88)
        - Charles Pyllik (Box 88)
        - Rockbestos Wire & Cable Co./Cerro-Flex (Box 88)
        - Saybrook Laundry, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - Summerwood Assoc - Hearing, 1977 September (Box 88)
        - Tomarack Corp - Hearing, 1975 June (Box 88)
        - W. Webster Car Wash (Box 88)
      - Orange (Box 88)
        - Orange Misc. (Box 88)
        - 400 Boston Post Road Devel (Box 88)
        - Branch Motor Transportation Co. (Box 88)
        - Cantor Residence (Box 88)
        - Douglas Enterprise (Box 88)
        - Internal Machine P.C. (Box 88)
        - National Screw Prod (Box 88)
        - Knights, Inc. (Box 88)
        - Adley Express (Box 89)
        - L & R Metal Testing (Box 89)